<form>
    <field>
        <id>general.enabled</id>
        <label>Enable VPN Link</label>
        <type>checkbox</type>
        <help>Enable automatic NAT, DNS, and routing rules for WireGuard VPN clients.</help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>general.mode</id>
        <label>Client Mode</label>
        <type>dropdown</type>
        <help><![CDATA[
            <b>Intranet Only</b>: VPN clients can only access specified LAN subnets. No internet access.<br/>
            <b>LAN Equivalent</b>: VPN clients are treated like LAN devices — they inherit all existing
            firewall rules including domain-based gateway routing. Traffic is masqueraded on every exit interface.
        ]]></help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>general.autoNat</id>
        <label>Auto NAT</label>
        <type>checkbox</type>
        <help>Automatically create outbound NAT (SNAT) on every exit interface. Includes loopback NAT for DNS access.</help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>general.dnsSync</id>
        <label>DNS Sync</label>
        <type>checkbox</type>
        <help>Automatically add WireGuard tunnel subnets to DNS access control (Unbound ACL / AdGuard bind).</help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>general.dnsTopology</id>
        <label>DNS Topology</label>
        <type>dropdown</type>
        <help><![CDATA[
            <b>Auto-Detect</b>: Automatically detect if AdGuard Home is installed.<br/>
            <b>Unbound Only</b>: Plugin syncs Unbound ACL.<br/>
            <b>AdGuard Home + Unbound</b>: Plugin ensures AdGuard listens on WG IPs and syncs Unbound ACL.
        ]]></help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>general.lanInterface</id>
        <label>LAN Interface(s)</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help><![CDATA[
            Comma-separated LAN interface names (e.g. "opt1" or "opt1,opt2").<br/>
            <b>LAN Equivalent</b>: VPN traffic is masqueraded on these interfaces to inherit their firewall rules.<br/>
            <b>Intranet Only</b>: NAT is applied on these interfaces for return traffic.
        ]]></help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>general.natInterfaces</id>
        <label>NAT Interfaces (VPN Gateways)</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help><![CDATA[
            Additional interfaces to auto-generate outbound NAT on. Use this for VPN gateway interfaces
            (e.g. "ovpnc1,ovpnc2" for OpenVPN clients used as gateways).<br/>
            WAN and LAN interfaces are always included automatically.
        ]]></help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>general.lanSubnets</id>
        <label>LAN Subnets (Intranet Mode)</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help>Comma-separated subnets accessible in Intranet Only mode (e.g. "192.168.1.0/24"). Ignored in LAN Equivalent mode.</help>
    </field>
</form>
